A Guide to the Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Riverfront
  - Early Results and Preliminary Conclusion for the Second Street Business District Committee of Richmond Renaissance, Inc.; March 1983 (Box A18)
  - Haliburton Company Annual Report 1989 (Box A18)
  - Newspaper Articles: Richmond Business 1988-1990 (Box A18)
  - Nine Minutes to Retail; December 1989 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000: Technical Report; May 1988 (Box A18)
  - Carnegie Cooperation of New York (Box A18)
  - Info Index 1993 (Box A18)
  - Plans/Reports Index 1993-1994 (Box A18)
  - CATD Schedule/Checklist 1993-1994 (Box A18)
  - Scripts 1993 (Box A18)
  - Circa Limited 1989 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Ward: Financial (Box A18)
  - K Jellstrom and Lee, Inc. 1988-1989 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Center Banking 1988-1990 (Box A18)
  - J.B. Cruz 1989-1990 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Center 1989-1991 (Box A18)
  - Laveer Partners 1989-1990 (Box A18)
  - McGuire Woods Battle and Boothe 1989-1990 (Box A18)
  - Rountrey and Associates, Inc. 1988 (Box A18)
  - Plans for Jackson Center (Box A18)
  - Gateway Visitor Center Design Proposal (Box A18)
  - Miscellaneous 1983-1989 (Box A18)
  - Richmond Tomorrow (Box A19)
  - American Security Bank 1989 (Box A19)
  - Riverview Landing: Financial Analysis 1990 (Box A19)
  - Richmond Renaissance Executive Committee Briefing 1990 (Box A19)
  - Financial Statements; January-December 1992 (Box A19)
  - Riverview Landing: A Mixed Use Development 1991 (Box A19)
  - Richmond: We're Still Making History; June 1986 (Box A19)
  - Richmond Renaissance: General Journal Entries 1994-1995 (Box A19)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park (Box A19)
  - St. George's Town Heritage (Box A19)
  - Economic Development Strategy for New York's Capital City (Box A19)
  - Confederate Navy Yard (Box A19)
  - America's First Freedom (Box A19)
  - Hippodrome (Box A19)
  - Community of Interest; December 1993 (Box A19)
  - General Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box A19)
  - Meetings: Valentine Museum 1993 (Box A19)
  - Jackson to the James It 1989 (Box A19)
  - African American Sports Hall of Fame 1993 (Box A19)
  - Blues Armory 1985-1992 (Box A19)
  - CATD Description (Box A19)
  - CATD Econ. Feasibility 1993 (Box A19)
  - Imprisims; Vol. 21, No. 3 (Box A19)
  - Play Structures (Box A19)
  - Windows (Box A19)
  - Windows: Central Presentation (Box A19)
  - History Never Same (Box A20)
  - VR Proximity Map (Box A20)
  - Riverside Arieal (Box A20)
  - Pattern Building Third Floor (Box A20)
  - Pattern Building Second Floor (Box A20)
  - Fall of Richmond Fire (Box A20)
  - African American Sports Hall of Fame (Box A20)
  - Gabriel (Box A20)
  - Jackson Ward (Box A20)
  - Gabriel/Patrick Henry (Box A20)
  - Poor Color/Images (Box A20)
  - Chimbrazo (Box A20)
  - Valentine Riverside (Box A20)
  - City Themed as a Destination (Box A20)
  - Richmond Riverfront Development Corporation 1993 (Box A20)
  - Clarence Townes 1993-1994 (Box A20)
  - Richmond Renaissance Letters 1994 (Box A20)
  - Division of Labor 1993 (Box A20)
  - Richmond City Schools (Box A20)
  - Navy Yard (Box A20)
  - The Livable City Almanac 1992 (Box A20)
  - Manufacturing Matters 1987 (Box A20)
  - Interwoven Destinies: Cities and the Nation 1993 (Box A20)
  - Presidential Debate: University of Richmond 1992 (Box A20)
  - Virginia General Assembly; Session Summary 1994 (Box A20)
  - The Final Campaign and other Civil War Sites in Central Virginia 1994 (Box A20)
  - Virginia Adjusted Gross Income by Class and Locality (Box A20)
  - Virginia Personal Income 1980-1990 (Box A20)
  - Animation of the City Washington, D.C. Downtown Sudy 1986 (Box A20)
  - Horse Racing in New Kent County in the Virginia Tradition of Excellence; November 1992 (Box A20)
  - Central Richmond Association Forum Feb. 25, 1993 (Box A20)
  - Richmond City, Virginia Pamphlet 1992 (Box A20)
  - Back to the Future: Richmond at the Crossroads (Box A20)
  - Richmond Surroundings; November 1991 (Box A20)
  - Broad Street Residential Study; May 1986 (Box A20)
  - Proposal for a Housing Market Analysis of Downtown Richmond, Va; December 1986 (Box A20)
  - The Affordable Community 1980's (Box A20)
  - Executive Summary of the City of Richmond: Federal/Empowerment Zone/Enterprise Community Application; June 1994 (Box A20)
  - Central Richmond Association: Downtown Data Book; January 1986 (Box A20)
  - Governor's Regional Economic Development Advisory Council; July 1994 (Box A20)
  - Canal Walk Brick Orders (Box A20)
  - FRP: Credit Committee 1985 (Box A21)
  - FRP: 19 E. Broad Street Waller and Company Jewlers 1983-1985 (Box A21)
  - FRP: Design Committee 1984-1985 (Box A21)
  - FRP: 2 West Broad Street Ovoutee's Social Club; October 1985 (Box A21)
  - BSTF: General Meeting March 7, 1985 (Box A21)
  - BSTF: General Meeting October 25, 1985 (Box A21)
  - BSTF: Contract Services 1984-1985 (Box A21)
  - BSTF: Meetings 1984-1985 (Box A21)
  - BSTF: Letterhead; March 1985 (Box A21)
  - Broad Street Project: Broad Street Task Force 1984-1986 (Box A21)
  - FRP: 1-3 Broad Street, James S. Sease 1985-1986 (Box A21)
  - FRP: 6 East Broad Street, James S. Sease 1986 (Box A21)
  - Broad-Grace Retail: Consultant Proposals 1985 (Box A21)
  - FRP: 417-19 E. Broad Street, Patricia and Howard Marks 1985 (Box A21)
  - Broad Street Facade Renovation Project 1985 (Box A21)
  - FRP: Prospects 1985 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Broad Street Civic Association 1986 (Box A21)
  - BGR Downtown Retail Development 1983-1985 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Organization and Management 1982-1986 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Advertising and Promotion 1985 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Economic Restructuring 1985-1986 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Realtors and Appraisers 1985 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Market Analysis 1985-1986 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Design and Physical Improvements 1984 (Box A21)
  - BGR: Hammer, Siler George Associates 1985-1986 (Box A21)
  - Market Center Development Corporation of Baltimore (Box A21)
  - BA: Multi-Media Show-Media at Large- Really Richmond 1984-1985 (Box A21)
  - BA: Multi-Media Show Media Wrights Proposal; January 1985 (Box A21)
  - BA: Collaborative Arts Commitee of Sixteen (Box A21)
  - Museum Collaborative 1985 (Box A21)
  - BA: Collaborative Arts August 6, 1984 (Box A21)
  - Broad Street Theaters 1984-1986 (Box A21)
  - BGR: New Idea Corps Study; May 1982 (Box A21)
  - Brook Crossing (Box A21)
  - BGR: Historic District Designations 1984-1986 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Ida Centralized MGMT. Technical Assistance Program 1985-1986 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Misc. Development Proposals and Activities 1984-1985 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Street Vendors 1984 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Arts District Development Proposals 1982 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Public Improvemtents 1983-1985 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Private (Building) Improvements 1981-1984 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Property Uses 1984 (Box A22)
  - BA: Collaborative Arts 1983-1984 (Box A22)
  - Collaborative Arts 1985 (Box A22)
  - BA: Collaborative Arts Survey Design and Analysis 1984 (Box A22)
  - BGR: Property of Ownership 1983-1985 (Box A22)
  - Broad Street 1984 (Box A22)
  - Broad Street Corridor Ownership Data (Masters) November 2, 1983 (Box A22)
  - BA: Report by G. Fletcher; June 1985 (Box A22)
- Education
  - Restructuring: General 1990-1993 (Box A22)
  - Schlechty 1993 (Box A22)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond (LMR) 1991-1993 (Box A22)
  - Total Quality Management (TQM) (Box A22)
  - Virginia: VBC, State Vision 1992 (Box A22)
  - Speaker Information 1992 (Box A22)
  - Education Committee 1992 (Box A22)
  - Directory of Violence Prevention Richmond Metro Area 1990-1993 (Box A22)
  - Report and Recommendations of the Richmond Renaissance Education Initiative April 21, 1994 (Box A22)
  - Adopted School Board Budget 1992-1993 (Box A22)
  - Concerns Iss 24; January 1990 (Box A22)
  - Allies in Education: Schools and Businesses Working Together for At-Risk Youth; Fall 1987 (Box A22)
  - Long-Range Plan; October 1992 (Box A22)
  - Business Partnership Activities-RPS: Students First 1991-1992 (Box A22)
  - The Demographics of Education and Service Delivery Systems 1989 (Box A22)
  - Access; Fall 1993 (Box A22)
  - Issues in Restructuring Schools; Fall 1993 (Box A22)
  - Forginig New Relationships Through Collaboration; July 1991 (Box A22)
  - Thinking Collaboratively: Ten Questions and Answers to Help Policy Makers Improve Children's Services 1991 (Box A22)
  - Community/School Dropout Prevention Program (Box A22)
  - Business and the Schools: A Guide to Effective Programs; Feb. 1992 (Box A22)
  - Richmond Renaissance Education Initiative Staff Development Committee Nov. 6, 1992 (Box A22)
  - A Proposal to Provide Planning Management Support to the Richmond Renaissance Education Initiative July 28, 1993 (Box A22)
  - Management Audit Non-Instructional Operations; December 1988 (Box A22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A23)
  - A Guide for Crafting a Profamily System of Education and Human Service; April 1993 (Box A23)
  - Richmond Renaissance Education Intiative: Learning Barriers Study Committee November 6, 1992 (Box A23)
  - Student Assessment Committee Nov. 6, 1992 (Box A22)
  - Curriculum and Mentoring Report 1992 (Box A23)
  - Structure Committee 1992 (Box A23)
  - School Assessment Subcommittee November 6, 1992 (Box A23)
  - Richmond Renaissance Education Intiative Staff Assessment Committee Final Report November 6, 1992 (Box A23)
  - Pre-School Committee: Richmond Renaissance Education Initiative November 1, 1992 (Box A23)
  - Comprehensive Education Reform for Alabama 1992 (Box A23)
  - Cities in Schools-Richmond, Va.: A Community Assessment-Feasibility Study; December 1992 (Box A23)
  - Report and Recommendations of the Richmond Renaissance Education Initiative April 21, 1994 (Box A23)
  - America's Choice: High Skills or Low Wages!; June 1990 (Box A23)
  - Commission for Educational Excellence June 18, 1991 (Box A23)
  - America's Agenda; Spring, Winter 1992 (Box A23)
  - Travel/Tourism Facts and Figures 1987-1992 (Box A23)
  - Clay Street Office Building: Mkt. and Econ. Feasibility Study 1983 (Box A23)
  - The Third and Clay Building: a Proposed Office Building to be Located at 300 East Clay Street-Richmond, Va (Box A23)
  - Capital Guaranty Insured; January 1994 (Box A23)
  - Map of Duluth, Minnesota (Box A23)
  - Information Prepared for the Valentine Museum: Crestar March 11, 1994 (Box A23)
  - Virginia Economic Indicators 1993 (Box A23)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (Box A23)
  - Virginia's Blue Ridge Mountain (Box A23)
  - Thomas and Means Associates Inc.; December 1987 (Box A23)
  - Research Division Report: Economic Impacts of Arts Cultural Institution; November 1977 (Box A23)
  - Virgninia's Workforce 2000 (Box A23)
  - The Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce: Focus on Our Region 1994 (Box A23)
  - Valentine Museum September 15-16, 1993 (Box A23)
  - Richmond Renaissance Newsletters; June 1985-1987 (Box A23)
  - Clay Street 1984 (Box A23)
  - Jackson Ward 1992-1993 (Box A24)
  - Financial Records 1989 (Box A24)
  - Monthly Financial Statements 1987 (Box A24)
  - Monthly Financial Statements: Consolidated Richmond Renaissance 1986 (Box A24)
  - Monthly Financial Statements 1986 (Box A24)
  - South of the James Development Committee 1989-1990 (Box A25)
  - Architect Rendering (Box A25)
  - Payroll Records 1988 (Box A25)
  - General Ledger and Transaction Journals 1985 (Box A25)
  - Journal Generals Ledger 1984 (Box A25)
  - General Ledger and Transaction Journals and Chart of Accounts (Prepared by ADP) 1986 (Box A25)
  - Monthly Financial Statements: Consolidated RR (Prepared by ADP) 1985 (Box A25)
  - General Pledges 1982 (Box A25)
  - Bank Reconciliations 1986-1988 (Box A26)
  - General Contribution Pledges 1986-1989 (Box A26)
  - General Contributions Pledges-Receivable Ledger 1988-1989 (Box A26)
  - Presidential Design Awards 1984 (Box A26)
  - Housing and Development Reporter: Current Developments 1986-1987 (Box A26)
  - Housing and Development Reporter: Current Developments 1987 (Box A26)
  - Housing and Development Reporter: Current Developments 1987-1988 (Box A26)
  - Housing and Development Reporter: Reference File 1,2,3 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Program Planning and Management 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: SRL Housing and Demographic Survey 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Vision 2000 Communication Strategies 1988 (Box A27)
  - 30 Committee 1989 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: 2000 Project Committee 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward Development Committee 1984-1989 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Real Estate (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Planning 1987-1989 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Existing Conditions 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Consultant and Developers 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: VCU Opinion Survey; April 1988 (Box A27)
  - Black Enterprise Institute 1988-1989 (Box A27)
  - State Library Relocation 1988 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward: Brook Road 1982 (Box A27)
  - Potential Project Finance Sources 1988-1989 (Box A27)
  - Jackson Ward Day 1989 (Box A28)
  - Vision 2000 Neighborhood Offices 1988 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Second Street 1985, 1988 (Box A28)
  - Virginia Museum for Black History and Archives Inc.: Proposed Structure; July 1991 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Maggie L. Walker Historic Site 1982-1985 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Jackson Place 1989 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Vision 2000 Brochures (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 Development Workshop 2; May 1988 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Promo Campaign 1989 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: Tom Martinson 1988 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward: David Lee and Stull 1988 (Box A28)
  - Maggie L. Walker National Historic Site (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000; Survey Research; May 1988 (Box A28)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 Technical Appendix; May 1988 (Box A28)
  - Thomas and Means Associates Inc. November 30, 1987 (Box A28)
  - Option Agreement; May 1984 (Box A28)
  - City of Richmond Urban Design Plan (Box A28)
  - Main Street, Ohio; Dec. 1981 (Box A28)
  - Riverfront Flood Protection and Development Study; April 1979 (Box A28)
  - Character Conservation Plan; March 1977 (Box A28)
  - Strategies for Cities and Counties August 22, 1984 (Box A28)
  - Byrd National Airport (Box A28)
  - Richmond Economic Development Strategy; June 1983 (Box A28)
  - Proposal for Consulting Assistance in the Preparation of a Plan for Downtown Richmond February 14, 1983 (Box A28)
  - The Richmond Area: We're the Heart of Virginia (Box A28)
  - The Enterprise Development Company (Box A28)
  - Charter of Richmond 1982 (Box A28)
  - The Nonprofit as Entrepeneur; Feb.-March 1985 (Box A28)
  - Cultural Facilities in Mixed-Use Development (Box A28)
  - Facts: about Richmond (Box A28)
  - Waterloo Place (Box A28)
  - News about Indianapolis; April 1985 (Box A29)
  - Philadelphia (Box A29)
  - Writer's Group and Black Future 1985 (Box A29)
  - Wow! Baltimore 1984 (Box A29)
  - Countdown to Renaissance II: The NEw Way Corporate America Builds 1984 (Box A29)
  - Sally Heart Fulton 1982-1984 (Box A29)
  - UVB Transportation and Parking May 13, 1985 (Box A29)
  - Transportation; October 1982 (Box A29)
  - Richmond CBD Service Study; June 1983 (Box A29)
  - Research Materials 1981 (Box A29)
  - Revised Downtown Plan Issue Paper July 12, 1983 (Box A29)
  - Regional Data Report: An element of the Richmond Regional Policies Plan; June 1983 (Box A29)
  - Regional Policies Plan-Draft; June 1982 (Box A29)
  - Project One Area Parking Study January 5, 1983 (Box A29)
  - S.I.R. Study March 31, 1983 (Box A29)
  - Shockoe Bottom Revitalization 1983 (Box A29)
  - Capitol Area Housing Study December 24, 1982 (Box A29)
  - Sixth Street Festival Marketplace 1982-1983 (Box A29)
  - Sixth Street Festival Marketplace: Enterprise Development Company December 9, 1982 (Box A29)
  - Sixth Street Festival Marketplace November 12, 1982 (Box A29)
  - Downtown Development Projects: Fiscal and Economics 1984-1985 (Box A29)
  - Crime Prevention Through Enviromental Design; May 1983 (Box A29)
  - International Downtown-Executive Association (Box A29)
  - Economics Developments: A Statistical Study 1984 (Box A29)
  - Historic Streetcar Study 1984 (Box A29)
  - Historic Streetcar Study 1984 (Box A29)
  - Impacts of new Developments on Older Commercial Areas; Spring 1982 (Box A29)
  - Neighborhood Commercial Revitalization Stategy Plan; August 1982 (Box A29)
  - North Core Area 1969 (Box A29)
  - Northside Commercial Area Plan; October 1980 (Box A29)
  - A Strategy for Action for Downtown Richmond 1976-2000 (Box A29)
  - A Proposal to provide Consulting Services to the City of Richmond in the preparation of a Plan for Downtown Richmond February 15, 1983 (Box A29)
  - Economics of Amenities Richmond Case Study December 10, 1984 (Box A29)
  - The Incubator Building Nov. 19, 1985 (Box A29)
  - Report of the Capital City Government Commission June 29, 1981 (Box A29)
  - Master Plan; November 1982 (Box A29)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A29)
  - James River Discovery Program Canal Walk Brown's Island Improvements; April 1986 (Box A30)
  - AV: Conflicts and Interests Along the James River and Canal 1985 (Box A30)
  - Canal Walk Budget/Project Expenses Contingencies 1987-1988 (Box A30)
  - CPP Requisitions 1987-1988 (Box A30)
  - Brown's Island W-T/Project Management 1983 (Box A30)
  - RR Wt Contract Brown's Island Walkway 1983 (Box A30)
  - Tredegar Ball P.Q./Receipts 1985 (Box A30)
  - Contract Admin. 1988-1989 (Box A30)
  - Change Order 4 (a)/H and B 1987 (Box A30)
  - Canal Walk-Pts. A,B,C, and D 1987-1988 (Box A30)
  - Brown's Island Stairway-General 1983 (Box A30)
  - Tredegar Ball: receipts and copy of checks; June-July 1985 (Box A30)
  - Attendees-Tredegar Ball 1985 (Box A30)
  - Canal Walk Turnover to City 1987 (Box A30)
  - Bidders and Bids Canal Walk, Brown's Island (Box A30)
  - Tredegar Street Improvements February 9, 1987 (Box A30)
  - Outdoors Fund Grant Program Dec. 6, 1985 (Box A30)
  - Interior Contractor/Materials 1985-1986 (Box A30)
  - KIOSK-Futile HOH Designs (Box A30)
  - RFP/Contractor Choices 1985 (Box A30)
  - Brown's Island Walkway and Stairway 1983 (Box A30)
  - Wilbur Smith-Belle Island Bridge 1984-1986 (Box A30)
  - McCarthy: Pier Damage 1985 (Box A31)
  - Cross Bridge 1985-1986 (Box A31)
  - Virginia Environment Endowment Grant Contract 1985-1986 (Box A31)
  - Virginia Environment and Endowment Application 1985 (Box A31)
  - Endorsements Commitments 1985 (Box A31)
  - Virginia Environmental Endowment 1986-1988 (Box A31)
  - Sprinklers/ Fountains 1987 (Box A31)
  - Theaters-LDR: Design Contracts 1985 (Box A31)
  - Feasibility Work 1985 (Box A31)
  - HRF Efforts 1987 (Box A31)
  - Theater Options 1986 (Box A31)
  - Theater Packaging Material (Box A31)
  - Dr. Fred Shaia; Correspondence, Agreements, etc 1985 (Box A31)
  - Cox/Symphony Effect 1984 (Box A31)
  - Ideas/Strategy 1984-1985 (Box A31)
  - Hammer, Silver, George Study (Box A31)
  - Photos, Prints, etc. (Box A31)
  - Cost Estimates/Models 1985 (Box A31)
  - Marketing Prospectors 1986-1987 (Box A31)
  - Cox and Other Background Mats 1983, 1986 (Box A31)
  - Press Articles 1984-1985 (Box A31)
  - Extra Copies of Addenda 2 and 3-Redesign (Box A31)
  - II 1983-1986 (Box A31)
  - Requests Form Mark Hirth 1989 (Box A31)
  - Pledges-James River Discovery Project 1987-1989 (Box A31)
  - Richmond Renaissance, Inc. General Pledges and Payments Worksheets 1987 (Box A31)
  - Economic Census form NC-9923 (Requested extension to file) 1988 (Box A31)
  - SIC Revision Classification Statements-Required by Va. Unemployment Compensation Act Feb. 17, 1988 (Box A31)
  - Property and Equipment 1989 (Box A31)
  - Payroll 1984-1986 (Box A31)
  - Forms 941-Current Year and Circular 1988 (Box A31)
  - Form 940 Federal Unemployment (F.U.T.A.)-Current Year 1986-1988 (Box A31)
  - Forms 1099 Rec'd by Richmond Renaissance form other Organizations; January 1989 (Box A31)
  - Federal 980 1982 (Box A31)
  - Forms 1099-Misc. 1986-1988 (Box A31)
  - Virginia Unemployment Q. Returns-Current Year 1986-1988 (Box A32)
  - Form 990 1984-1988 (Box A32)
  - AETNA Problems 1986-1987 (Box A32)
  - W-2's and W-3's 1986-1989 (Box A32)
  - Richmond Renaissance Monthly Payroll Prepared by ADP (Box A32)
  - James River Discovery Program: Cash Records 1985-1988 (Box A32)
  - Richmond Renaissance Payroll Records 1987 (Box A32)
  - Richmond Renaissance Payroll Earning Records 1985 (Box A32)
  - Accounting Book Records 1982 (Box A32)
  - Buy-A-Brick Project: Charge Card Agreement with Bank of Virginia June 16, 1988 (Box A32)
  - IDA-Fort Worth 1986 (Box A32)
  - Contributions January 9, 1986 (Box A32)
  - National Council for Urban Economic Development 1986 (Box A32)
  - Goals and Programs for Richmond Renaissance 1986-1987 (Box A32)
  - Floodwall 1986 (Box A32)
  - Astoria Canal Walk Brick 1986-1987 (Box A32)
  - Bound Reports-Sixth Street Market Place Vol. 1-4 (Box A33)
  - Jackson Center Vol. 1 and 2 (Box A34)
  - Richmond Renaissance 1986, 1987 (Box A34)
  - Budget 1987 (Box A34)
  - Complimentary-Miscellaneous 1986-1988 (Box A34)
  - Deposit Slips (Box A34)
  - Richmond Renaissance In Office Processing-Batch A-X 1986, 1987 (Box A34)
  - James River Corporation 1986 (Box A34)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A34)
  - Office of Peter Walker, Martha Schwartz (Box A34)
  - River City Company 1986-1987 (Box A34)
  - Randall Evans 1986 (Box A34)
  - Clarence Townes Jr. 1987 (Box A34)
  - Canal Walk Brick Bank Statements, Deposits and Back-up 1986-1988 (Box A34)
  - Robert Olson 1987 (Box A34)
  - National Endowment For Arts 1984-1986 (Box A34)
  - Partners for Livable Places 1986-1987 (Box A34)
  - Arts Council Orders 1987-1988 (Box A35)
  - State Penitentiary 1987-1988 (Box A35)
  - Arts and Advisory Committee; de Pilars-Chairman 1986 (Box A35)
  - An Agenda for Downtown Richmond (Box A35)
  - Riverfront Sculpture 1986-1987 (Box A35)
  - Ramada Renaissance Hotel 1985-1987 (Box A35)
  - Blues Armory Collaboration 1985 (Box A35)
  - Parking Stike Force 1985-1986 (Box A35)
  - Housing 1985-1986 (Box A35)
  - Economics of Amenity Phase II 1986 (Box A35)
  - Economic Dev. Committee (Correspondence) 1986 (Box A35)
  - Canal Walk Bricks-Bach 17-31 (Box A35)
  - Statue of Relgious Freedom 1985-1986 (Box A35)
  - Vending Overview (Box A35)
  - Submarine 1986 (Box A35)
  - Urban Design Committee 1986-1987 (Box A35)
  - Cochrane Property 1986 (Box A35)
  - Environmental Education Center 1991-1992 (Box A35)
  - Virginia Environmental Endowment/Cabell 1988-1993 (Box A35)
  - Education Center 1991 (Box A35)
  - Pump and Haul Sewage System (Box A35)
  - Environmental Education Center 1993 (Box A35)
  - Belle Isle Program/Math-Science Center/VCU (Box A35)
  - Shed and Misc. (Box A35)
  - Wildlife Fish and Game Department 1985-1991 (Box A35)
  - JRC/CSX (T.S.) 1993 (Box A35)
  - Trails Cost 1993 (Box A35)
  - BIB Plaza 1991 (Box A35)
  - Wildlife Fish and Game Department-Contracts and Reimbursements 1991-1992 (Box A35)
  - Fountain Marker 1991 (Box A35)
  - Fountain 1992 (Box A35)
  - Fountain Construction 1993 (Box A35)
  - Trails 1991-1992 (Box A35)
  - Conservation Fund 1990 (Box A36)
  - James River Roundtable 1986-1987 (Box A36)
  - Feasibility Study of Fish Passage Facilities on the James River (Box A36)
  - Trust for Public Land 1992-1993 (Box A36)
  - Sisters of the Blessed Sacrament 1993 (Box A36)
  - Hydroplant 1988-1989 (Box A36)
  - Belle Isle Environmental Education Center 1991 (Box A36)
  - The Richmond Whitewater Center (Box A36)
  - Construction Specifications 7th Street Fountain October 10, 1992 (Box A36)
  - Richmond Riverfront Improvements Program (Box A36)
  - River Times 1987 (Box A36)
  - Breaching of Low Head Dams for Fish Passage on the James River; December 1985 (Box A36)
  - Environmental Education Center Contract Admin 1992-1993 (Box A36)
  - The Future of the Capital Area: Vol. 1 and 2; May 1988 (Box A36)
  - Back to the Future: Richmond at the Crossroads (Box A36)